NATASHA ALRIDGE

7218 Birchmont Dr. Rowlett, Tx 75089 · (214) 586-7577 Nalridge@gmail.com

Newly graduated LVN licensed in Texas with 5 years of hospital, LTACH and rehabilitation nursing assistant experience. Looking for a position that involves a Health Care facility where I can utilize my nursing education and training, as well as my interpersonal skills to provide the highest level of care.

EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2016 – OCTOBER 2016

PATIENT CARE TECHNICIAN, BAYLOR SCOTT AND WHITE HEALTH

Assisted nurses with wound care for pressure ulcers, bed sores, and surgical site wounds. Followed infection control procedures.

Assisted residents with bathing, dressing, feeding, lifting and transferring.

Ensured safety and well-being of patients.

NOVEMBER 2012 – JULY 2013

REHABILITATION TECHNICIAN, BAYLOR INSTITUTE FOR REHABILITAION

Helped develop care plans for patients with complex needs and assisted patients with using their rehabilitation equipment.

Assisted patients with bathing, dressing, hygiene and grooming.

Monitored fluid intake and output levels.

Maintained cleaned and organized rehabilitation rooms and equipment.

JUNE 2012 – OCTOBER 2012

CERTIFIED NURSE ASSISTANT, CHRISTIAN CARE CENTER

Collects patient specimens and data, including vital signs, input/output and other delegated measurements.

Followed safe lifting techniques and individual resident lifting instructions.

Turned and positioned patients to maintain comfort and minimize problems.

EDUCATION

JULY 2018

LICENSED VOCATIONAL NURSE, CONCORDE CAREER COLLEGE

FEBRUARY 2016

GED, EL CENTRO COLLEGE